linkslister.com 2014-04-29

# GotLinks.com Free Link Exchange Service

## Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register for an account on GotLinks.com. 

When registering on our website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them. 

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs. 

Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. 

The email address you provide for registering will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your account. 

**How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. 

Whenever payments are made online, sensitive information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. Payments to GotLinks.com are made through PayPal or 2Checkout.com and both companies provide SSL encryption. 

Your personal data is encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

**Do we use cookies?** Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information 

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

**Terms and Conditions**  
Please also visit our Terms of Service section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of GotLinks.com at <http://www.gotlinks.com/tos.php>, <http://www.gotlinks.com/tos_prem.php> and <http://www.gotlinks.com/aff_tos.php>

**Your Consent**  
By using the GotLinks.com service, you consent to our web site privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

**Next Net Media, LLC  
http://www.Gotlinks.com  
316 California Ave. #804  
Reno, NV 89509  
USA  
info@nextnetmedia.com  
1-800-737-5820  
**
